(Sheldon:)Do we really have to go
to Mrs. Wolowitz's house?
(Amy:)We do.
(Amy:)And I expect you
to be on your best behavior.
(Sheldon:)Now I know how the
African slaves felt.
(Sheldon:)Being dragged from their homes
to labor under the
yoke of the white man.
(Amy:)Are you honestly comparing
Thanksgiving dinner
(Amy:)at Wolowitz's mom's with
one of the greatest tragedies
(Amy:)in the history of mankind?
(Penny:)Yes.
(Penny:)Sheldon, you can have
a nice Thanksgiving anywhere.
(Penny:)I spent one in Vegas.
(Leonard:)You did?
(Penny:)Yeah, back when I was dating Zack.
(Penny:)It was actually more fun
than I thought.
(Penny:)We gambled, we went to one
of those cheesy wedding chapels,
(Penny:)we had a really good
turkey dinner.
(Penny:)Which was surprising,
since we were at a strip club.
(Leonard:)Wait, you went to a chapel?
(Sheldon:)-Yeah.
-Why?
(Penny:)We had one of those
silly fake weddings.
(Leonard:)Penny...
(Leonard:)You know those are real, right?